If you buy a Ferrari, they'll deliver it
for free to your local Ferrari
dealership, apparently. Or you can pay
500 pounds, have a tour of the factory
in Maranello, which you travel to at
your own expense, and then drive the car
home. I don't know if you noticed that,
but by framing it as a tour of the
factory, they've got you to pay to
collect your own car. Uh Rolls-Royce and
Maserati made their cars cheaper through
innovation. They stopped exhibiting them
at car shows, where they look expensive,
and they started exhibiting them at
yacht and plane shows. If you've been
looking at Lear jets, Gulfstreams, and
Sunseekers all afternoon, a 250,000 euro
car is an impulse buy. By the way, if
you allow people to pay for something
contactlessly, it feels 15% cheaper, by
the way.